Guide to the Larry Polansky Papers MSS.405
Fales Library and Special Collections
Larry Polansky Papers
1937- ongoing
1970-2010
Fales Library and Special Collections
Polansky, Larry, 1954-
MSS.405
77.50 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons, 72 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 8 tall manuscript boxes, 23 flat boxes, 9 oversize flat boxes, 2 media boxes, and 1 flat-file folder
268 Gigabytes in 127,537 computer files.
917 audiocassettes
131 sound cassettes (dat)
19 videocassettes (betamax)
9 videocassettes (vhs)
2 videocassettes (video 8)
2 videoreels (1/2 inch)
131 Reels audio reels
1 websites in 1 archived website.
Larry Polansky (b. 1954) is an American music composer, performer, teacher, writer, and computer programmer. The Larry Polansky Papers document an individual's ongoing career in the creation, performance, and education of music, beginning in the 1970s to the mid-2010s. The bulk of these papers consist of Polansky's extensive output as a composer through work files, performance notes, and sound recordings. Event ephemera and audiovisual recordings document musical performances and festival/conference appearances from the 1980s through the mid-2010s. This collection contains office files for Frog Peak Music, an artists' collective co-founded by Polansky and Jody Diamond, as well as administrative files for Lingua Press, a company absorbed by Frog Peak Music in 1995. Polansky's departmental files from Mills College and Dartmouth College dating from the 1980s through 2013 can also be found in this collection. Writing and project files in both paper and electronic format document Polansky's extensive and varied interests within the modern music field, covering subjects such as music composition, psychoacoustics and formal perception, new tuning systems, instrumentation, and computer programs for algorithmic composition. Of note are his work files on his profiles and analysis of various composers and their works including Johanna Magdalena Beyer, Ruth Crawford Seeger, and James Tenney. Polansky's personal files contain correspondence and subject files related to his work, illustrating his extensive network of colleagues and friends within his field. Large groupings of regularly backed up computer files containing a combination of personal and professional documents from the 1980s to the 2010s are in this collection.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Larry Polansky, 2014. The accession number associated with this gift is 2014.405.
Take Down Policy
Archived websites are made accessible for purposes of education and research. NYU Libraries have given attribution to rights holders when possible; however, due to the nature of archival collections, we are not always able to identify this information. If you hold the rights to materials in our archived websites that are unattributed, please let us know so that we may maintain accurate information about these materials. If you are a rights holder and are concerned that you have found material on this website for which you have not granted permission (or is not covered by a copyright exception under US copyright laws), you may request the removal of the material from our site by submitting a notice, with the elements described below, to: fales.library@nyu.edu. Please include the following in your notice: Identification of the material that you believe to be infringing and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material; your contact information, such as an address, telephone number, and email address; a statement that you are the owner, or authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed and that you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and made under penalty of perjury; and your physical or electronic signature. Upon receiving a notice that includes the details listed above, we will remove the allegedly infringing material from public view while we assess the issues identified in your notice.
Appraisal
Robots.txt was ignored with the permission of the content owner. Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of https://wayback.archive-it.org/4049/*/http://eamusic.dartmouth.edu/~larry/ in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
Appraisal
Twenty-nine commercial audio CDs already available to researchers in the Avery Fisher Center for Music and Media were separated and removed from this collection.
Four damaged data discs, a dvd, and 11 floppy disks were removed from the collection.
Duplicate copies of concert ephemera and publications were removed from the collection. Paper and electronic material containing student records or faculty information, as well as personal material outside the scope of collecting were separated and removed from the collection.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in six series, one of which has been further arranged into two subseries.
The series and subseries arrangement is as follows:
Series I. Compositions and Arrangements
Series II. Event Ephemera
Series III. Frog Peak Music
Subseries III. A. General
Subseries III. B. Lingua Press and Kenneth Gaburo
Series IV. Writings and Projects
Series V. Teaching and Appearances
Series VI. Personal
Biographical Note
Larry Polansky is a composer, performer, teacher, editor, and writer. Polansky taught at the Mills College Center for Contemporary Music from 1980-1990, where he also co-authored with Phil Burk and David Rosenboom the computer music language Hierarchical Music Specification Language (HMSL). He is the Emeritus Strauss Professor of Music at Dartmouth College, where he taught from the 1990s to 2013, and in 2019 retired from his teaching position at University of California, Santa Cruz. His articles are published in many journals including Perspectives of New Music, the Journal of Music Theory, and the Leonardo Music Journal (of which he was the founding editor). In 2004, at the request of composer Ruth Crawford Seeger's estate, he completed and edited Seeger's major monograph The Music of American Folk Song. His writings on American music include works on James Tenney, Ruth Crawford Seeger, Lou Harrison, and Johanna Magdalena Beyer. As a performer of primarily guitar and mandolin, Polansky has premiered and recorded contemporary works on his own, as well as with several contemporary music ensembles. As a recording artist, his solo albums include Artifact, and Cold Blue, and his music is widely anthologized on a number of recording labels. Among his other projects, Polansky is co-founder and co-director of Frog Peak Music, a composers' collective and in 2010, he wrote the film score for Stacey Steers' Night Hunter. He is a recipient of a number of prizes, commissions, and awards, including Guggenheim, Fulbright, and Mellon New Directions Fellowships.
Custodial History
The website was selected by curators and captured through the use of Archive-It. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact special.collections@nyu.edu. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Electronic Records Policies and Procedures
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted.
An access terminal for a large portion of the born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Some born-digital materials have not been transferred and may not be available to researchers. Researchers may request access copies. To request that material be transferred, or if you are unsure if material has been transferred, please contact fales.library@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Archived Website Policies and Procedures
Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
Scope and Contents
This collection documents Larry Polansky's ongoing work in the contemporary music field from the 1970s to the mid-2010s through music compositions, recordings, teaching notes, business and project files, as well as concert ephemera in paper and electronic formats. Business files in this collection were generated by Polansky's artists' collective, Frog Peak Music, and contain promotional catalogs, publicity material, as well as client files which provide insight into the operation of a collective devoted to publishing and producing experimental and unique works by composers active during the 1980s into the 2000s. Office files for Lingua Press contain administrative material, as well as documentation of the company's 1995 acquisition by Frog Peak Music. Polansky's extensive writings on modern music theory, composers, and compositions are represented in this collection through paper and electronic versions of notes and edited drafts of articles, papers, and reviews written throughout the 1970s to the 2000s. Paper and electronic files, as well as audio recordings document Polansky's various projects, including his music recording career, development of his computer program Hierarchical Music Specification Language (HMSL), and his project with Indonesian composers and performers from the 1980s with Jody Diamond. Lectures notes and slides, correspondence, and faculty-related material in this collection relate to Polansky's music composition and theory classes he taught at Mills College Center for Contemporary Music from the 1980s to 1990s, and Dartmouth College from 1990 to 2013. This collection also contains his archived website; his backed up personal and professional electronic files; news clippings; correspondence and subject files; and his private audiocassette collection can also be found in this collection.
Separated Materials
131 items of Polansky's inventoried/numbered personal cassette tape collection were transferred to the Avery Fisher Center for Music and Media on 10/2/2018. These cassettes were commercially produced, widely distributed recordings. A list of titles transferred, as well as the complete list of cassettes in his personal collection can be found in the Curator's collection files.
Composers -- United States -- 20th century; Composers -- United States -- 21st century; Music -- Manuscripts.; Contemporary music.; scores (documents for music); Gamelan.; Audiocassettes.; Transparencies.; Lecture notes.; Composition (Music) -- 21st century.; Composition (Music) -- 20th century; Instrumental Music.; Correspondence.; Concert programs; Music -- Computer programs.; Music theory.; Computer music; Canons, fugues, etc.; Polansky, Larry, 1954-; Dartmouth College. Department of Music; Diamond, Jody; Feldman, Anita, 1951-; Frog Peak Music; Gaburo, Kenneth; Lingua Press; Mills College. Center for Contemporary Music; Partch, Harry, 1901-1974; Seeger, Ruth Crawford, 1901-1953; Tenney, James
- Series I. Compositions and Arrangements, 1975-2013; 22 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 13 manuscript boxes, 8 tall manuscript boxes, 3 flat boxes, and 5 oversize flat boxes; 7.37 Gigabytes in 1,742 computer files.; 70 audiocassettes; 48 sound cassettes (dat); 57 Reels
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in alphabetical order by title. The inventory lists either in an alphabetical range by title or individually if the title has more than one folder. Oversized titles are listed individually.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains paper and electronic work files, sheet music, video and sound recordings related to Polansky's original compositions and arrangements dating from the mid-1970s to 2013. His work files illustrate the creative workflow of composing contemporary musical compositions through handwritten drafts, master copies of works, edited scores with performance notes and directions, computer program reports, and differing versions of pieces which were altered over the years. This series contains a significant amount of work files for Lonesome Road (The Crawford Variations), a set of variations by Polansky on a work by composer Ruth Crawford Seeger. This series also contains work files for Bedhaya Guthrie/Bedhaya Sadra; Four Voice Canon (numbers 2-22c); Jargon; Milwaukee Blues; Psaltery; Sasha's Song; Piano Study #5 and Yitgadal. Audio recordings of individual pieces including Four Voice Canons, Psaltery, Milwaukee Blues, and Sasha's Song can be found in this series. Other recordings of works can be found in Series IV. This series also contains Polansky's composition idea notebooks and handwritten untitled and unpublished sheet music.
  - 3 Cello Tunes, 1998-2010; cuid25280 (Box 1, Folder 1, Box 76)
  - 3 New Hampshire Songs -- Approaching the Azimuth..., 1979-2012; cuid25931 (Box 1, Folder 2-20)
  - 3 Pieces for 2 Pianos, 2007; cuid25708 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - 8 Lines for Voice and 8 Instructions, 2012; cuid25680 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - 17 Simple Melodies, undated; cuid25681 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - 34 Chords Christian Wolf in Hanover and South Royalton, 1998-1999; cuid25682 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - 85 Chords, 2006; cuid25683 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Al Hitai, 1986; cuid25334 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Angel Variations, undated; cuid25689 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Another You, 1991; cuid25335 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Around the Horn, undated; cuid25690 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - B'midbar (Numbers), 2008; cuid25932 (Box 1, Folder 21, Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Bedhaya Sadra / Bedhaya Guthrie, 1989-1992, undated; cuid25281 (Box 1, Folder 22-24, Box 76, Folder 7, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_405_ER_50)
  - Birthday Waltz for Corky Harris, Opus #9991 -- Col Yomim, 1977-2013, undated; cuid25282 (Box 2, Folder 1-15)
  - Brujo, 1981; cuid25336 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Canon for Flute / Copy of Vellum, 1979; cuid25337 (Box 72, Folder 4, Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Canon in 2 Voices, 2008; cuid25684 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Canons (Graphic Score), undated; cuid25338 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Carry Me Long, undated; cuid25339 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - The Casten Variation, 2000-2001; cuid25884 (Box 2, Folder 7, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_405_ER_5, E-records FA_MSS_405_ER_55)
  - Choir / Empi's Solo, 1979, 1995-2000; cuid25685 (Box 76, Folder 9, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_405_ER_1)
  - Collected Scores Book I, 1983; cuid25283 (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
  - Common Things -- Entreaty, 1978-2013, undated; cuid25284 (Box 2, Folder 18-28)
  - Compassion, 1997; cuid25340 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Corrected, Loose Compositions, undated; cuid25686 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Dismission, 2006; cuid25687 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Drafts, Notebooks, 1977-2013, undated; cuid25315 (Box 9, Folder 1-16, Box 74, Folder 1-5, Box 78, Folder 13-14)
  - Essays for String Quartet 1-3, 1999, undated; cuid25285 (Box 2, Folder 29-30, Box 76, Folder 12)
  - ET Morphogenes B-Flat -- Fifty Miles of Elbow Room, 1978-1993, undated; cuid25286 (Box 2, Folder 31-34)
  - For Jim, Ben and Lou (Three Pieces for Harp, Guitar and Percussion), 1995, 2008, undated; cuid25287 (Box 3, Folder 1, Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Four Bass Studies (What to Do When the Night Comes), 1983; cuid25678 (Box 3, Folder 2, Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Four Children's Songs, undated; cuid25933 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Four Easy American Tunes (Guitar and Flute), 1980; cuid25679 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Four Voice Canon, 1978, 1990, 1992; cuid25288 (Box 3, Folder 4, Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Four Voice Canon #2--12, 3--8, 2000; cuid25289 (Box 3, Folder 5, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_405_ER_53)
  - Four Voice Canon #4, 1978, undated; cuid25290 (Box 3, Folder 6-8, Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Four Voice Canon #5, 1986, 2001, 2004; cuid25291 (Box 3, Folder 9, Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Four Voice Canon #6, 1986; cuid25292 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Four Voice Canon #7, 1990, undated; cuid25293 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Four Voice Canon #8, undated; cuid25294 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Four Voice Canon #12 Doggerel, 1999; cuid25295 (Box 3, Folder 13, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_405_ER_51, E-records FA_MSS_405_ER_2)
  - Four Voice Canon #13, #15, 2000-2003; cuid25296 (Box 3, Folder 14, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_405_ER_52, E-records FA_MSS_405_ER_3, E-records FA_MSS_405_ER_21)
  - Four Voice Canon #14, 2002; cuid25886 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_405_ER_69)
  - Four Voice Canon #18, #20, #20a, 2002-2004; cuid25297 (Box 3, Folder 15, Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Four Voice Canon #22a, #22c, 2008; cuid25298 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Free Horn, 2005, 2011-2012; cuid25299 (Box 3, Folder 17, Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Fuging Tune in G -- Horse Turds and Roses, 1979-2013; cuid25934 (Box 3, Folder 18-29)
  - Getting Rid of the Glue, 1978; cuid25688 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Glockentood, 2000; cuid25343 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Gottlieb Variations, 1985; cuid25929 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Guitar Exercises / Single Strings, undated; cuid25344 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Haiga 1C, 1988, 1991, 2011; cuid25341 (Box 72, Folder 8, Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Hensley Variations, 1985, 1996; cuid25345 (Box 72, Folder 13, Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Here to Stay, 1983; cuid25930 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Hineh Matov, undated; cuid25342 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Horn, 1990, 1993, undated; cuid25346 (Box 72, Folder 14, Box 76, Folder 19, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_405_ER_4)
  - I, 2007, 2011; cuid25710 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Idgty -- Ivtoo, 2001-2007, undated; cuid25300 (Box 4, Folder 1-5)
  - If I Only Had a Brain..., 2000; cuid25347 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - III. Canon in Four Voices, undated; cuid25709 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - iiiisiv joan, 2006; cuid25705 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - In Memoriam: Stefan Wolpe, 1976; cuid25348 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - In that Bright World, undated; cuid25349 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - ivt, 2000; cuid25706 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - ivtoo, 2000-2001; cuid25707 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Jargon, 2005, 2012; cuid25301 (Box 4, Folder 6-9, Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Joint Round -- Leave Logs for Frogs!, 2005-2012; cuid25302 (Box 4, Folder 10-13)
  - Ladies Auxiliary / Draft, 2006; cuid25704 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Lines, 1978; cuid25352 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Lissatood, 2004; cuid25703 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Little Maggie, 1983-1984, undated; cuid25350 (Box 4, Folder 14, Box 72, Folder 19, Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Lonesome Road (The Crawford Variations), 1989-2005, undated; cuid25303 (Box 4, Folder 15-17, Box 5, Folder 1-9, Box 6, Folder 1, Box 72, Folder 20, Box 79, Folder 1-5, Box 80, Folder 1-4)
  - Los Angeles -- Lullaby for Lucia, 2005-2012; cuid25304 (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
  - Milk and Honey, undated; cuid25353 (Box 6, Folder 4, Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Milwaukee Blues, 1984-1987, 1990; cuid25305 (Box 6, Folder 5-6, Box 73, Folder 2-3)
  - Misdirection -- Riddled and Ragged, 1977-2013, undated; cuid25306 (Box 6, Folder 7-33)
  - Movement in E Major for John Cage, 1996, undated; cuid25354 (Box 73, Folder 4, Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Movement for Andréa Smith, 1978; cuid25927 (Box 73, Folder 4, Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Movement for Lou Harrison, 1977, undated; cuid25702 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Noratood, 2004; cuid25355 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Now My Dear Companions, 2000-2001; cuid25700 (Box 77, Folder 9, Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Ontslaan (toontood), 2008; cuid25701 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Parting Hand, undated; cuid25356 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Patty's on the Turnpike, 1980; cuid25357 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Performance Notes, undated; cuid25699 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Piano Study #1 for Carl Ruggles, 1981; cuid25697 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Piano Study #5, 2000-2002; cuid25885 (Box 6, Folder 22, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_405_ER_54, E-records FA_MSS_405_ER_32)
  - Piker, undated; cuid25698 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Prelude, 1997; cuid25696 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Quartet in F, 1978; cuid25358 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Rebecca's (part 2) Pencil Score, "Parts", undated; cuid25695 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Resultant Harmonies, undated; cuid25359 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Roads to Chimacum, 1992-1993; cuid25307 (Box 6, Folder 34, Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Rob -- See You Around With..., 1982-2009, undated; cuid25308 (Box 7, Folder 2-10)
  - Roll over Beethoven, Guitar II, 1983; cuid25360 (Box 73, Folder 10, Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Sasha's Song, 1983; cuid25694 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Saskia's Piano Doodle, 1999; cuid25361 (Box 73, Folder 11, Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Six Declarations, 2000-2001; cuid25928 (Box 73, Folder 11, Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Shma, 1979, circa 1982; cuid25309 (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
  - Shutting Up -- Three Rimbaud Settings, 1977-2013, undated; cuid25310 (Box 7, Folder 13-28)
  - Silence Study #2 (Clarinet and Bassoon), 1976; cuid25693 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Simple Song, 2011; cuid25691 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Six Declarations, 2001; cuid25692 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Song 2 Arrangement, 2005, 2008; cuid25362 (Box 73, Folder 12, Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Songs and Toods, Drafts, 2005-2006; cuid25711 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Sound Recordings on Audiocassette, 1977-1991; cuid25858 (Box 97, Box 100, Box 101)
  - Sound Recordings on Digital Audio Tape (DAT), 1993-2003; cuid25863 (Box 102)
  - Sound Recordings on Open Reel, 1978-1987; cuid25868 (Box 104, Box 105, Box 106, Box 107, Box 108, Box 109, Box 110, Box 111, Box 112, Box 113, Box 114)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    1" Open Reel (Audio), Count: 2 1/2" Open Reel (Audio), Count: 4 1/4" Open Reel (Audio), Count: 51
  - Suite from Lonesome Road, 1996; cuid25351 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Sweet Betsy from Pike, undated; cuid25712 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Tape Piece for Dance (Nancy Bryan), circa 1980s; cuid25713 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Tetherball, 1998, 2000; cuid25714 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - A Thank You Round..., 2000; cuid25363 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Three Fiddler Tune Transcriptions, 2000; cuid25715 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Three Monk Tunes, 1982; cuid25364 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Three Pieces for Bass and Psalterion, 2006; cuid25716 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Three Pieces for Joe and Sarah, First Draft, 2007; cuid25717 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Three Pieces for Two Pianos, 2007; cuid25718 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Three Songs -- Withdrawn Round, 1976-2012, undated; cuid25311 (Box 8, Folder 1-18)
  - The Time is Now, 1987; cuid25365 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Torah Tropes (Shabat Morning), undated; cuid25719 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Trio Canon, 2002; cuid25720 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Trombone Piece, Movement III / I Drafts, 2011; cuid25721 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Two Can Float as Cheap as One, 1979; cuid25722 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Two Geminopeddies for Annika, 1999; cuid25366 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Two Minute Warning, 1998; cuid25723 (Box 78, Folder 10)